Hello, I am a candidate for
the election of the director
representing employees
shareholders for the group
Société Générale, I can represent
YOU. I propose you to
now tell you about our
differences.
I do not seek to be
director, I don't want
be able to boast of being
Group Ambassador
my importance cannot be measured
to the number of direct report
But my pride
will be to represent you
ensuring a dialogue of equals
with each other, with my good
sense, with my knowledge of
the bank, I will bring
hopefully a hightlight
complementary and therefore useful
union and executives visions
for decisions
of the Board of Directors
Our proposal from Caroline and
I is , I believe, singular.
We think it is
desirable that employees
shareholders be presented
by independant employees
close to the fields but
also close to the places of
power
Independent :  not to be
under the authority of a
organization (union or
investor association)
in order to avoid dogmatic
posture.
Independent to stay free
to represent you.
Close to the fields so that the
bank players, at all levels
facing customers
with the quality of the relationship,
that brings value, but
also people from
back-office that maintain
the functioning of the bank
at the best cost.
Close to carry your voice
Also close to
power in order to simply
to make your voice
audible on a daily basis.
In conclusion, we are
committed to the group SG
to defend the
employee values regarding
their work (the
recognition of this work)
their capital (the valorisation
of this capital)
But at the same time, we
want to defend the values
of employees in the broadest sense of the term
what commits or engages them,
motivates them, their engine, their
motivation, what makes their
pride, our pride to
work for the group.
I add to all this that I have
management experience
through commitments
associations, such as
as secretary of OGEC
for about 15 years,
but also as
as a director of a
family business during
nearly 20 years
and finally through a
training on the
banking regulation, the
risk management and
internal control for
directors and officers,
training that I receive on
the 2nd  October
Do ypu adhere to this mode of
governance, to our vision of
the bank, to the objectives
to which we
Caroline and I, are committed to ?
You think the bank has a
playing card for a
bright future ?  If so : don't forget
to vote for your
best candidate between
Sept 28th and Oct 9th
on ESALIA and
SHARINGBOX.
I am counting on you
and above all
take care of yourself.
Translated with www.DeepL.com/Translator (free version)