Jérôme Lepagnol
Candidate for the election of
directors of
the director representing
employee shareholders
The importance of this election
for you is something
essential and our goal
for this election is to
represent you.
I propose to represent
YOU at the board
of directos so that "what
you know" as
collaborator is made
audible and useful for
decisions of the board. For the
management and HR for example
the right profiles need
recognition and not only in
term of remuneration
the environment, the
comfort and safety at the
work, clarity of managerial
vision, participation
to the decisions, the sharing of
information are essential to us.
And it is possible to influence
these elements. => Let's discuss your
vision of these subjects
The conditions of performing our banking business
changee, is changing, and above all, will change.
Again you know it.
Competition or cooperation
with the Fintech -startups in the field of
of finance- ,
sometimes strained relationships
with the supervisor in Europe and in
the world. Banking concentration,
changes in the habits of
our customers are probably
inevitable in the future
You know the assets
and capabilities
of the bank to cope with it
in this new world =>  well share with us
your perspective on the transformations
opportunities that could
change the future of the bank
for all of us.
On all these points,
Caroline and I bring
our vision of the bank that
changes with the involvment of
responsible finance, CSR,
the uses of the technologies of
information
and finally with the opportunities
related to artificial intelligence
and science data  in
the financial field. We do not
let's not pretend to know everything
that's why your contribution
is essential at our side.
How to ensure this sharing
information? Sitting on the Board
implies to be bound to the secrecy of
information that is exchanged there.
So I won't be able to
relate what happens there.
On the other hand, I propose to be
the relay to the Board and the
general management on all
your feedback from the
fields. And to make it I am
currently building an application
and a website for this information relay
This system, reserved for employees of the
Société Générale Group
will also allow to animate the debate
between us on opportunities, but also
to exchange from person to person
in a private way.
An essential point for your
confidence: this platform,
will be independent of any
organization, of any trade union
and even the management of the
bank, so that your word
is not deformed.
I will ensure the anonymity of
feedback to the
board and management
general. The technical device
(server development host)
will be funded by elements
remuneration for the role of administrator
A significant portion of this remuneration will be
also donated to a charity.
I will really represent you!